question_data = [
{"category":"General Knowledge","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"Video streaming website YouTube was purchased in it&#039;s entirety by Facebook for US$1.65 billion in stock.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"General Knowledge","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"Gumbo is a stew that originated in Louisiana.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"General Knowledge","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"French is an official language in Canada.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"General Knowledge","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"Nutella is produced by the German company Ferrero.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"General Knowledge","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"Bulls are attracted to the color red.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"General Knowledge","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"The Sun rises from the North.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"General Knowledge","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"Adolf Hitler was born in Australia. ","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"General Knowledge","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"Romanian belongs to the Romance language family, shared with French, Spanish, Portuguese and Italian. ","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"General Knowledge","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"&quot;27 Club&quot; is a term used to refer to a list of famous actors, musicians, and artists who died at the age of 27.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"General Knowledge","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"Dihydrogen Monoxide was banned due to health risks after being discovered in 1983 inside swimming pools and drinking water.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"General Knowledge","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"The National Animal of Scotland is the Unicorn.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"General Knowledge","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"Vietnam&#039;s national flag is a red star in front of a yellow background.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"General Knowledge","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"A pasodoble is a type of Italian pasta sauce.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"General Knowledge","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"Slovakia is a member of European Union-","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"General Knowledge","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"The mitochondria is the powerhouse of the cell.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]}
]